<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>shiny on Dylan McKenna - Fundamentals of Analytics</title>
    <link>/categories/shiny/</link>
    <description>Recent content in shiny on Dylan McKenna - Fundamentals of Analytics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/shiny/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Final Project</title>
      <link>/2021/06/27/final-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021/06/27/final-project/</guid>
      <description>Description of DatasetThe dataset used for this project is the Daily Weather in the U.S., 2017. The data is collected by 1589 stations throughout the United States and Canada. The collected data consists of 15 variables; however, only 8 variables were used for this project.
How does the temperature change with latitude?It is common sense to expect the temperature to decrease moving farther from the equator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assignment 05 - Exploratory Data Analysis - V2</title>
      <link>/2021/06/26/assignment-05-exploratory-data-analysis-v2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021/06/26/assignment-05-exploratory-data-analysis-v2/</guid>
      <description>Assignmnet 5 - Exploratory Data AnalysisThis is the submission for Assignment 5 - EDA.
Dataset: City of Chicago - Crime - 2001 to PresentThe dataset used for this assignment was the City of Chicago Crime Statistics data. To reduce the file size, the data is reflective of the year 2019 and the year 2020. This data is taken from the Chicago Police Departments publicly available data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assignment 04 - Using ShinyApp</title>
      <link>/2021/06/18/assignment04-using-shinyapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021/06/18/assignment04-using-shinyapp/</guid>
      <description>Assignment 4 - Using ShinyAppThis assignment involved creating an interactive post with ShinyApp.
Click Here for ShinyApp!
You can download the dataset below.
Homeruns per TeamThe following chart shows the amount of homeruns (HR) per team in each year.
The Top 5 Teams are highlighted.
An interesting observation is that the HR leaders in early 2000’s were much higher than the years afterward. One possible reason for the decrease of HR’s could be that steroid testing began during the 2003 season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assignment A04 - Shiny</title>
      <link>/2021/06/14/assignment-a04-shiny/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021/06/14/assignment-a04-shiny/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
